(Sheldon:)My queen can now
take your rook from below.
(Penny:)So that means I lose, right?
It's over!
(Sheldon:)If I make this move...
(Sheldon:)But I won't because
we're having too much fun.
(Penny:)-Okay, let's take a break.
-We're all out of alcohol.
(Penny:)I wasn't going to get alcohol.
(Penny:)Gosh, I wonder what Leonard's doing
right now. I miss him so much.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you'd like,
we could call him.
(Sheldon:)I mean that you could call him.
(Sheldon:)As I've explained, the absence
of my friends does not cause me pain.
(Sheldon:)As rock and roll bad boy Paul Simon
once said,
"I am a rock. I am an iiiisland."
(Penny:)-I'm calling him.
-Oh, goodie! Put him on speakerphone!
I (DANCE MUSIC PLAYS) I